RG 016, Department of Public Health
Connecticut State Library
- Series 17. Medical Registration Applications, 1893-1976; 86 cubic feet
  - Medical Quality Assurance, 1941-1976
    - RN ENDO/Reciprocity licensure files, 1915-1941; 1996-017
      - 721-1400, 1930 January 14-December 15 (Box 2)
      - 1401-2160, 1930 December 15-1934 December 15 (Box 3)
      - 2161-2900, 1934 December 15-1938 February 10 (Box 4)
      - 1901-3600, 1937 February 10-1940 May 8 (Box 5)
      - 3601-3900, 1940 May 5-1941 January 9 (Box 6)
- Series 19. New Haven County. Census Statistics, 1884-1897; T000501; .25 cubic feet
  - Census Statistics, 1884-1897; 1 volume (Volume Item)
- Series 20. State Board of Health, 1878-1917; 1 cubic foot
  - T000507, .25 cubic feet
    - Quarterly and special meeting minutes, 1898-1901 (Box Envelope)
  - 1987-030A, .75 cubic feet
    - Quarterly and special meeting minutes, 1878-1917
      - 1878-1884, 1 volume (Box 1)
      - 1884 September-1901 January, 1 volume (Box 1)
      - 1901 January-1912 November, 1 volume (Box 1)
      - 1913 January-1917 June, 1 volume (Box 1)
      - 1898, 1 envelope (Box 1)
      - 1902, 1 envelope (Box 1)
      - 1903, 1 envelope (Box 1)
      - 1904, 1 envelope (Box 1)
      - 1905, 1 envelope (Box 1)
    - Report of inspection of Hartford County Temporary Home, 1892; 1 envelope (Box 1)
    - State health officials biographical data, 1959 June; 1 folder (Box 1)
    - Report of proceeding at second annual conference of the health officials of Connecticut, Hartford., 1904 December 14-15; 1 volume (Box 1)
    - Reports of duties, 1947 (Box 2)
      - Administration (Box 2)
      - Hairdressing (Box 2)
      - Local Health Administrator (Box 2)
      - Accounts & supplies (Box 2)
      - Sanitary engineering (Box 2)
      - Irrevertible diseases (Box 2)
      - Public health instruction (Box 2)
      - Public health nursing (Box 2)
      - Venereal diseases (Box 2)
      - Vital statistics (Box 2)
      - Mental hygiene (Box 2)
      - Maternal & child hygiene (Box 2)
      - Crippled children (Box 2)
      - Dental hygiene (Box 2)
      - Laboratory (Box 2)
      - Industrial hygiene (Box 2)
    - Occupational Health Section material, 1967-1966; 1 envelope (Box Item 3)
- Series 21. Tuberculosis Commission / Tuberculosis Control, Hospital Care and Rehabilitation Division., 1909-1988; 3.25 cubic feet
  - 1985-029
    - Minutes
      - 1909-1912, 1 volume (Volume Item 1)
      - 1912-1913, 1 volume (Volume Item 2)
      - 1913, 1 volume (Volume Item 3)
      - 1975-1978, 1 volume (Volume Item 4)
    - Administrative Files, circa 1930-1979 (Box Box 5)
    - Photographs, circa 1920-1929, 1950-1959 (Box Box 5)
    - Scrapbooks, circa 1950-1959 (Box Box 6)
  - 1989-051
    - Photographs, 1979-1988 (Box Box 1)
  - 1998-017
    - Photographs, 1957-1958 (Box Envelope)
  - T003188
    - School vaccine plan, circa 1937 (Box Envelope)
- Series 24. Hospital and Medical Care Division, 1966-1978
  - Institutional Licensure Files
    - 1985-026C
      - Chronic and Convalescent Nursing Homes
        - A-HA, 1977 (Box 1)
        - HE-PO, 1977 (Box 2)
        - PR-Z, 1977 (Box 3)
      - Rest Homes with Nursing Supervision (Home for Aged), 1977 (Box 4)
      - General Hospitals
        - Backus-Rockville, 1977 (Box 5)
        - St. Francis - Yale, 1977 (Box 6)
      - Chronic Disease Hospitals, 1977 (Box 7)
      - Outpatient Clinics, 1977 (Box 8)
      - Homes for Aged
        - Al-Jo, 1977 (Box 9)
        - Ke-We, 1977 (Box 10)
    - 1986-010A
      - Chronic and Convalescent Nursing Homes
        - A-Hi, 1978 (Box 1)
        - Hig-Sa, 1978 (Box 2)
        - Sea-Th, 1978 (Box 3)
        - Tu-Z, 1978 (Box 4)
      - Rest Homes with Nursing Supervision (Home for Aged), 1978 (Box 5)
      - General Hospitals
        - Backus-Newington, 1978 (Box 6)
        - Norwalk-Yale, 1978 (Box 7)
      - Chronic Disease Hospitals, 1978 (Box 8)
      - Outpatient Clinics, 1978 (Box 9)
      - Home for the Aged
        - A-L, 1978 (Box 10)
        - M-W, 1978 (Box 11)
    - 1989-035
      Retained as a sample of the official certification process for skilled nursing facilities, group homes, and mental health facilities.
      On label: "SNF/ICF/MR Certifications"
      - Case files, A-M (Box 1)
      - Case files, N-Z (Box 2)
      - Dead files, Intermediate Care Facilities, A-Z (Box 3)
      - Dead files, Skilled Nursing Facilities, A-M (Box 4)
      - Dead files, Skilled Nursing Facilities, N-Z (Box 5)
  - Agricultural Workers Hospital File
    - 2013-042
      - Agricultural Workers Hospital, Windsor, Connecticut, 1966-1975; 3 folders (Box 1)
- Series 25. Dr. Stanley H. Osborne collection, 1799-1979; 12.5 cubic feet
  - T000520
    - Miscellaneous books, 1799-1945 (Box 1)
      - Webster, Noah. A Brief History of Epidemic and Pestilential Diseases; with the Principal Phenomena of the Physical World, which Precede and Accompany Them and Observations Deduced From the Facts Stated. Hartford, Conn.: Hudson & Goodwin, 1799 (Box 1)
      - Medical pamphlets, 1880-1881 (Box 1)
      - Emergency Medical Service, Operation Book. Connecticut War Council, 1945 June 1 (Box 1)
    - Local health surveys
      - Questionnaire, List of towns (Box 2)
      - Ansonia, Derby, Oxford, Seymour, and Shelton, 1955, 1957 (Box 2)
      - Bridgeport, 1942 (Box 2)
      - Bridgeport, 1959; 2 volumes (Box 2)
      - Bristol, 1957 (Box 2)
      - Danbury, 1929, 1964 (Box 2)
      - Darien, 1948 (Box 2)
      - East Hartford, 1958 (Box 2)
      - East Haven, 1949 (Box 2)
      - Fairfield, 1946 (Box 2)
      - Greenwich, 1925 (Box 2)
      - Hamden, 1939 (Box 2)
      - Hartford, 1949 (Box 2)
      - Manchester, 1941 (Box 2)
      - Meriden, 1931 (Box 2)
      - Middletown, 1918 (Box 2)
      - Milford, 1940 (Box 2)
      - New Britain, 1940 (Box 2)
      - New Britain, 1960 (Box 2)
      - New Canaan, 1948 (Box 2)
      - New Haven, 1953, 1962 (Box 2)
      - New London, 1943 (Box 3)
      - North Haven, 1928 (Box 3)
      - Norwalk, 1940 (Box 3)
      - Norwich, 1950 (Box 3)
      - Norwich, 1950 (Box 3)
      - Rockville, 1947 (Box 3)
      - Stratford, 1930 (Box 3)
      - Rockville, 1947 (Box 3)
      - Stratford, 1930 (Box 3)
      - Thomaston, 1950 (Box 3)
      - Torrington, 1951 (Box 3)
      - Wallingford, 1943 (Box 3)
      - Waterbury, 1939, 1961, 1966 (Box 3)
      - Watertown (Box 3)
      - West Hartford, 1930, 1951 (Box 3)
      - Westport, 1939 (Box 3)
      - Wethersfield, 1951 (Box 3)
      - Willimantic, East Windham County, 1955, 1958 (Box 3)
      - Winsted, 1930 (Box 3)
    - Special Reports
      - 1914-1948, 2 folders (Box 4)
      - Connecticut Prisons, 1895, 1904 (Box 4)
      - Connecticut Physicians in the Civil War, circa 1961-1970 (Box 4)
      - Newsletter, 1942 February-1945 October (Box 4)
      - Bureau of Child Hygiene, Budgets, 1929-1934 (Box 4)
      - Biographies (Box 4)
    - Attorney General's Opinions
      - Index, Barber-Eclectics, 1919-1943 (Box 5)
      - Embalming-National Industrial Recovery Act, 1919-1943 (Box 5)
      - Natureopathy-Water, 1919-1943 (Box 5)
      - Index. Barber-Hairdressing, 1938-1959 (Box 5)
      - Healing Arts-Miscellaneous, 1938-1959 (Box 5)
      - Natureopathy-X-ray, 1938-1959 (Box 5)
      - Index, Air Pollution-County Homes, 1960-1971 (Box 6)
      - Cremation-Psychologists, 1960-1971 (Box 6)
      - Public Health Council-X-ray, 1960-1971 (Box 6)
      - Index, Abortion-Health Facilities, 1971-1979 (Box 6)
      - Health Offices-Public Health Council, 1971-1979 (Box 6)
      - Registrations-Water, 1971-1979 (Box 6)
    - Connecticut Public Health Association, 1918-1949 (Box 6)
    - Memorabilia (Box 7)
      - Connecticut State Medical Society (Box 7)
      - Floods, 1936, 1938, 1955 (Box 7)
      - Dr. Stanley H. Osborne, His life and career (Box 7)
      - Dr. Stanley H. Osborne, Honorary certificates, 1914-1971 (Box 7)
        Plus 2 oversize items in map case.
      - Plaques, 1964, undated; 3 items (Box 7)
      - Guest book for dedication of the Stanley H. Osborn, M.D. Library, 1965 June 11 (Box 7)
  - 1986-038
    - Scrapbooks
      - 1918-1922, 1 volume (Volume Item 1)
      - circa 1919-1925, 1 volume (Volume Item 2)
      - 1922-1925, 1 volume (Volume Item 3)
      - 1923-1925, 1 volume (Volume Item 4)
      - 1924-1928, 1 volume (Volume Item 5)
      - 1925-1927, 1 volume (Volume Item 6)
      - 1927, 1 volume (Volume Item 7)
      - 1927-1928, 1 volume (Volume Item 8)
      - 1920, 1938-1947, 1 volume (Volume Item 9)
      - 1946-1947, 1 bundle (Volume Item 10)
        Newspapers with articles on natureopathy.
      - 1948, 1 volume (Volume Item 11)
        Includes congratulatory letter and photograph.
      - 1953-1954, 1 unbound volume in oversize box (Box Box 12)
      - 1954-1956, 1 volume (Volume Item 13)
        Includes clippings re new state office building, 1929; and proposed new Health Dept. building, 1931-1932.
      - 1956-1958, 1 volume (Volume Item 14)
      - 1958-1960, 1 volume (Volume Item 15)
      - 1959-1961, 1 volume (Volume Item 16)
      - 1961-1962, 1 volume (Volume Item 17)
      - 1962, 1 volume (Volume Item 18)
      - 1962-1963, 1 volume (Volume Item 19)
      - 1963-1966, 1 volume (Volume Item 20)
      - 1966-1967, 1 unbound volume in oversize box (Box Box 21)
      - 1969-1970, 1961-1972, 2 unbound volumes in oversize box (Box Box 22)
- Series 26. Commission on Hospitals and Health Care, 1974-1987; 1991-002; 20 cubic feet
  - Meeting folders, 1974-1987
    - 1974 September-1976 June (Box 1)
    - 1976 July-1977 December (Box 2)
    - 1978 January-December (Box 3)
    - 1979 January-August (Box 4)
    - 1979 September-1980 June (Box 5)
    - 1980 July-August (Box 6)
    - 1980 August-1981 February (Box 7)
    - 1981 March-September (Box 8)
    - 1981 October-1982 January (Box 9)
    - 1982 February-August (Box 10)
    - 1982 September-1983 May (Box 11)
    - 1983 May-June (Box 12)
    - 1983 June-July (Box 13)
    - 1983 July-1984 April (Box 14)
    - 1984 April-November (Box 15)
    - 1984 December-1985 June (Box 16)
    - 1985 July 2-October 29 (Box 17)
    - 1985 November 6-1986 June 3 (Box 18)
    - 1986 June 6-August 14 (Box 19)
    - 1986 August 14-1987 February 3 (Box 20)
- Series 27. Commissioner, 1944-1945, 1973; .75 cubic feet
  - Annual reports, 1944-1945; T000510; 2 volumes (Box Box 1)
  - Connecticut State Department of Health manual, 1973 March 6; 1995-045; 1 binder (Volume Item)
- Series 28. Community Nursing and Home Health Division, 1918-1980; 1988-028; 2 cubic feet
  - "The Public Health Nurse and the Mentally Ill Patient", Visiting Nurse Association of Hartford, Inc., 1967 (Box 1)
  - State aid and grants in aid, 1974-1977 (Box 1)
  - Historical MCH Manual, circa 1950-1959 (Box 1)
  - Historical Information Public Health Nursing in Connecticut, 1918/-1962 (Box 1)
  - State Aid for Public Health Nursing, 1935 July 1-1965 June 30 (Box 2)
  - State Aid for Public Health Nursing, 1954 July 1-1970 June 30 (Box 2)
  - State aid and grants in aid, 1977-1980 (Box 3)
  - State aid and grants in aid, 1970 July 1-1974 June 30 (Box 3)
  - Reports I Monthly Annual, 1953-1966 (Box 3)
  - Connecticut Valley Hospital Background I, circa 1964-1967 (Box 3)
  - Stamford Day Care Center, circa 1964-1967 (Box 3)
  - Care of Mentally Ill, Program Talks, Reports, Conferences, circa 1954-1969 (Box 3)
  - Social Workers PHN Nurses, circa 1953-1965 (Box 3)
  - Connecticut Valley Hospital, Correspondence, Minutes II, 1964-1968 (Box 3)
  - Norwich Referral Program, Scheduled Educational Meetings II, 1962-1967 (Box 3)
  - Reports II, Special Observations, Community Activities, 1954-1967 (Box 3)
- Series 29. Commission on Long Term Care, 1980-1990; 18 cubic feet
  - Coordinator's Records, 1980-1990; 1992-002; 16 cubic feet
    - Official Record of Minutes and copies of generated reports
      - Advisory Board minutes, 1980 July-1990 May 30 (Box 1)
      - Commission minutes, 1980 Ju,y-1989 December (Box 1)
        There were no meetings in 1990.
      - Compliance Report to Legislative Program Review and Investigations Committee, 1981 (Box 1)
      - Progress Reports and Legislative Mandates, 1983 (Box 1)
      - Coordinator's Recommendations - Final Report, 1990 (Box 1)
      - Agenda Packet for Final Three Quarterly Meetings, 1989 (Box 1)
      - Report on Review of Group Home Models as Community Residences for Persons with Traumatic Brain Injury and Similar Disorders, 1990 April (Box 1)
      - Documents, 1986 February, July,, 1987 July (Box 1)
        Commission and system goals and an inventory and update of selected state government activities and responsibilities in long term care.
        January 1987 missing. See State Library Government Documents.
      - Study on Coordination of Placements Between Whiting Forensic Institute and the Department of Correction, 1988 (Box 1)
      - Report on Coordinated Interagency Policy on Community Based Respite, 1988 March (Box 1)
      - Interagency Policy and Services Coordination Agreement (All major human service agencies and Attorney General's Office), 1987 April (Box 1)
      - Study of Nursing Pools in Connecticut, Mt. Vernon Report to Commission, Commission's Final Report, 1988 December-1989 January (Box 1)
      - Adopted Policies: Interagency Policies on Community Based Services and Nursing Home Pre-admission Screening for the Elderly, 1985 October (Box 1)
      - Report on Pre-admission Screening/Case Management to Legislators by Coordinator, 1985 February (Box 1)
      - Report on an Act Concerning Rate Setting and pay Procedures for Privately Operated Community Residences and Services for Mentally Retarded Persons: Experiences and Possible Adoptions to Other Disabled Populations - PA83-39 (Box 1)
      - Document Demonstrating Array and Continuum of Housing Arrangements, 1989 October (Box 1)
      - Documents Demonstrating Array of Continuum of Home Care Services, 1986 October (Box 1)
      - Advisory Board Recommendations on Treatment and Care of AIDS and ARC Patients in Nursing Homes, 1988 May (Box 1)
      - Advisory Board Position on Policy Recommendation on Cost Estimates for Nurse Aide Training (Box 1)
      - Coordinated Policy Position on Grandparenting of Certified Nurse Aides Employed by Nursing Facilities and Amendments to OBRA of 1987, 1989 October (Box 1)
      - Advisory Board Position on Avoidance of Patient Transfers when Terminating Provider Agreements, 1989 November (Box 1)
      - Commission to Study the Veterans' Home and Hospital - Sub-Committee report on Program Recommendations prepared by the Coordinator as Chair of the Sub-Committee, 1987 September (Box 1)
      - Strategic Planning Seminar on long Term Care - Agenda and Proceedings, 1984 November (Box 1)
      - Student Proposal for a State Coordinated Long Term Health Care Information System, 1989 (Box 1)
      - Special Report to the Commission on AIDS and Long Term Care, 1987 (Box 1)
      - LTC Financing Origin of Governor Appointed Commission, 1984-1986 (Box 1)
    - Correspondence, 1980-1990
      - Chronological files, 1980 July-1982 February (Box 2)
      - Chronological files, 1982 March-1983 December (Box 3)
      - Correspondence logs, 1980-1986 (Box 4)
      - Additional correspondence including correspondence regarding Statutory Amendment of 1983, 1982-1983 (Box 4)
      - Chronological files, 1984-1985 (Box 4)
      - Chronological files, 1986 (Box 5)
      - Correspondence logs, 1987-1988 (Box 6)
      - Chronological files, 1987-1990 (Box 6)
    - Back-up materials on Commission Meetings and Advisory Board (Box 7)
    - Issues (Box 8)
      - Complaint and Inquiry Management (Case Management Confidential) (Box 8)
      - MR & MI Client in Nursing Homes (Box 8)
      - "Waiting List" Law (Re: Nursing Homes) (Box 8)
      - PA-83-39 Community Residences (Box 9)
      - Rate Setting and Pay Procedures (Box 9)
      - PA-83-39 Community Residences (Box 9)
      - Rate Setting and Pay Procedures (Box 9)
      - Life Care - CT and Other States (Box 9)
      - Response to Governor on Federal Report Re: Nursing Homes (Box 10)
      - Brody's Chart (Box 10)
      - U.S. Senator Dodd's Hearing (Box 10)
      - Veterans' Home & Hospital Reports of Task Force and Coordinator (Box 10)
      - Interagency Policy on Community Based Services (Box 10)
      - Whiting Forensic Study (Box 10)
      - Personal Care Attendant Issues (Box 10)
      - Group Homes - Environmental Inspections (Box 10)
      - LTC Financing - Origin of Governor's Commission (Box 10)
      - Pre-Cabinet Proposal (Box 10)
      - Materials on Issues Affecting Individuals with Traumatic Brain Injury (Box 11)
        - Behavioral Management (Box 11)
        - Certificate of Need - Policy Issue (Box 11)
        - Group Home Pilot (Box 11)
        - Group Home Pilot Evaluation (Box 11)
        - Final Report on Pilot (Box 11)
        - Licensure Issue (Box 11)
      - Materials on Policy and Service Interagency Agreement Development of and Implementation Issues & Cases - Confidential (Box 11)
      - "Nursing Pool Study" as requested by State Legislature (Box 12)
      - Reports of "Mt Vernon Associates" (Box 12)
      - Final Report of Commission (Box 12)
      - Contract Materials (Box 12)
      - 1990 Legislative Proposal (Box 12)
      - Commission Activity Developing a Rate Setting Form (Box 12)
      - Nurse Aide Training - Establishing a Recommended Program Nurse Aide Survey and Conclusions (see box 14) OBRA 1987 - Grandparenting Issues (Box 13)
      - Nurses Aide Survey (Box 14)
      - Original Materials and Compiled data as obtained by the Department of labor for the Commission on Long Term Care (Box 14)
      - Agency Admin. State Files (Box 15)
      - Contracts (Box 15)
      - Forms 200 (Box 15)
      - Personal Files (Box 15)
      - Invoice (Box 15)
      - Budget (Box 16)
      - Travel (Box 16)
      - Contracts (Box 16)
      - Attendance (Box 16)
  - Administrative Records, 1986-1987; 1996-031; 2 cubic feet
    - Washington D.C. briefing materials, 1986 September 24 (Box 1)
    - Testimony: Public/Private (Box 1)
      - Alzheimers Disease (Box 1)
      - Rosalind Berman (Box 1)
      - Ron Durie, D.I.M. (Box 1)
      - Louis Halpryn (Box 1)
      - Kevin Kinsella (Box 1)
      - Karen Stone (Box 1)
    - Communications materials for Governor's on Private and Public Responsibilities for Financing Long Term Care for the Elderly (Box 1)
      - Communications plan for release of final Report & Gov.'s action plan (Box 1)
      - Copies of Commission and Governor's Offices press releases (Box 1)
      - Long term care media mailing list and 1 complete set of labels (Box 1)
      - Commission news clippings (Box 1)
      - Masters of Commission and Governor's Office press releases (Box 1)
    - Pitney Bowes - Mail Meter (Box 1)
    - Unfiled material (Box 1)
    - Media contacts (Box 1)
    - Commission correspondence, 1986 July-1987 June 30 (Box 2)
    - Governor's Commission on the Private & Public Financing of Long Term Care For the Elderly, Background Material (Box 2)
    - Governor's Commission on the Private & Public Financing of Long Term Care for the Elderly, Regular Meetings (Box 2)
    - Report Distribution, 1987 June-November 30 (Box 2)
    - Connecticut Public Hearing Testimony, 1986 September 3 (Box 2)
    - Governor's Commission on the Private & Public Financing of Long Term Care for the Elderly, Regular Meetings (Box 2)
    - Connecticut Public Hearing Testimony, 1986 September 3 (Box 2)
    - Commission HPFG Receipts, Etc. (Box 2)
    - Transcriptions of Speeches, Washington, D.C. Briefing, 1986 September 24 (Box 2)
- Series 30. Local Health Administration, 1931-1981; 12.5 cubic feet
  - Circulars, 1937-1972; T000503; 1 cubic foot
    - 1937-1947 (Box 1)
    - 1948-1962 (Box 2)
  - Annual Reports of Town Health Officials, 1931-1981; 1996-011; 11.5 cubic feet
    - Andover, 1931-1951 (Box 1)
    - Ansonia, 1936-1974 (Box 1)
    - Ashford, 1932-1979 (Box 1)
    - Avon, 1937-1979 (Box 1)
    - Barkhamsted, 1932-1970 (Box 1)
    - Beacon falls, 1933-1979 (Box 1)
    - Berlin, 1932-1975 (Box 1)
    - Bethany, 1931-1968 (Box 1)
    - Bethel, 1931-1978 (Box 1)
    - Bethlehem, 1931-1967 (Box 2)
    - Bloomfield, 1935-1979 (Box 2)
    - Bolton, 1932-1975 (Box 2)
    - Bozrah, 1932-1979 (Box 2)
    - Branford, 1931-1974 (Box 2)
    - Bridgeport, 1931-1979 (Box 2)
    - Bridgewater, 1931-1979 (Box 2)
    - Bristol, 1931-1981 (Box 2)
    - Brookfield, 1935-1975 (Box 3)
    - Brooklyn, 1931-1946 (Box 3)
    - Burlington, 1933-1971 (Box 3)
    - Canaan, 1934-1956 (Box 3)
    - Canterbury, 1931-1974 (Box 3)
    - Canton, 1931-1975 (Box 3)
    - Chaplin, 1931-1979 (Box 3)
    - Cheshire, 1933-1973 (Box 3)
    - Chester, 1941-1979 (Box 3)
    - Clinton, 1931-1969 (Box 3)
    - Colchester, 1931-1975 (Box 4)
    - Colebrook, 1931-1979 (Box 4)
    - Columbia, 1932-1951 (Box 4)
    - Cornwall, 1932-1959 (Box 4)
    - Coventry, 1931-1969 (Box 4)
    - Cromwell, 1931-1977 (Box 4)
    - Danbury, 1933-1979 (Box 4)
    - Darien, 1931-1979 (Box 4)
    - Deep River, 1044-1979 (Box 5)
    - Derby, 1931-1973 (Box 5)
    - Durham, 1933-1969 (Box 5)
    - East Granby, 1931-1976 (Box 5)
    - East Haddam, 1931-1971 (Box 5)
    - East Hampton, 1931-1979 (Box 5)
    - East Hartford, 1931-1979 (Box 5)
    - East Haven, 1931-1974 (Box 5)
    - East Lyme, 1934-1976 (Box 5)
    - East Windsor, 1931-1962 (Box 6)
    - Eastford, 1931-1974 (Box 6)
    - Easton, 1931-1966 (Box 6)
    - Ellington, 1933-1962 (Box 6)
    - Enfield, 1931-1974 (Box 6)
    - Essex, 1932-1975 (Box 6)
    - Fairfield, 1931-1976 (Box 6)
    - Farmington, 1931-1980 (Box 7)
    - Franklin, 1933-1952 (Box 7)
    - Glastonbury, 1935-1979 (Box 7)
    - Goshen, 1933-1942 (Box 7)
      See also Torrington Area Health District
    - Granby, 1931-1971 (Box 7)
    - Greenwich, 1931-1971 (Box 7)
    - Griswold, 1931-1979 (Box 7)
    - Groton, 1931-1979 (Box 7)
    - Haddam, 1931-1977 (Box 8)
    - Guilford, 1931-1978 (Box 8)
    - Hamden, 1931-1977 (Box 8)
    - Hampton, 1931-1979 (Box 8)
    - Hartford, 1931-1979 (Box 8)
    - Hartland, 1931-1971 (Box 8)
    - Harwinton, 1932-1967 (Box 8)
    - Hebron, 1931-1976 (Box 9)
    - Kent, 1939-1977 (Box 9)
    - Killingly, 1931-1974 (Box 9)
    - Killingworth, 1931-1965 (Box 9)
    - Lebanon, 1931-1976 (Box 9)
    - Ledyard, 1938-1974 (Box 9)
    - Lisbon, 1932-1979 (Box 9)
    - Litchfield, 1931-1966 (Box 9)
    - Lyme, 1935-1977 (Box 9)
    - Madison, 1931-1979 (Box 10)
    - Manchester, 1931-1973 (Box 10)
    - Mansfield, 1931-1979 (Box 10)
    - Marlborough, 1940-1979 (Box 10)
    - Meriden, 1931-1979 (Box 10)
    - Middlebury, 1931-1979 (Box 10)
    - Middlefield, 1937-1979 (Box 10)
    - Middletown, 1937-1981 (Box 11)
    - Milford, 1933-1978 (Box 11)
    - Monroe, 1931-1969 (Box 11)
    - Montville, 1931-1974 (Box 11)
    - Morris, 1942-1967 (Box 11)
    - Naugatuck, 1931-1979 (Box 11)
    - New Britain, 1931-1976 (Box 11)
    - New Canaan, 1931-1974 (Box 12)
    - New Fairfield, 1941-1977 (Box 12)
    - New Hartford, 1934-1970 (Box 12)
    - New Haven, 1931-1978 (Box 12)
    - New London, 1931-1977 (Box 12)
    - New Milford, 1931-1979 (Box 13)
    - Newington, 1931-1968 (Box 13)
    - Newtown, 1932-1973 (Box 13)
    - Norfolk, 1931-1970 (Box 13)
    - North Branford, 1931-1974 (Box 13)
    - North Canaan, 1937-1973 (Box 13)
    - North Haven, 1931-1977 (Box 13)
    - North Stonington, 1931-1974 (Box 14)
    - Norwalk, 1931-1979 (Box 14)
    - Norwich, 1931-1979 (Box 14)
    - Old Lyme, 1931-1979 (Box 14)
    - Old Saybrook, 1931-1975 (Box 14)
    - Orange, 1935-1979 (Box 14)
    - Oxford, 1931-1975 (Box 15)
    - Plainfield, 1941-1974 (Box 15)
    - Plainville, 1931-1979 (Box 15)
    - Plymouth, 1931-1978 (Box 15)
    - Pomfret, 1931-1974 (Box 15)
    - Portland, 1931-1979 (Box 15)
    - Preston, 1931-1979 (Box 15)